Finding Aid for the North American New Music Festival Sound Recordings, 1983-1993
State University of New York at Buffalo. Music Library
- Hard drives and accompanying documentation, 2017-2018, III.; 2 hard drives and 1 binder
  - Binder of accompanying documentation, 2017-2018, 1 binder (Box 10, Item 3)
NAF 607A. Metz, Donald: Wading (1992), on North American New Music Festival Concert 181, April 10, 1992, 11:00 p.m.
NAF 607B. Bacon, John: Percussion in space (1991), on North American New Music Festival Concert 181, April 10, 1992, 11:00 p.m.
NAF 619A. Cage, John: Four walls (1944), on North American New Music Festival Concert 183, April 11, 1992, 5:00 p.m.
NAF 619B. Satie, Erik: Genevieve de Brabant, opus posthumous (ca. 1899), on North American New Music Festival Concert 183, April 11, 1992, 5:00 p.m.
NAF 619C. Volans, Kevin: She who sleeps with a small blanket (1985), on North American New Music Festival Concert 184, April 11, 1992, 8:00 p.m.
NAF 619D. Baker, Michael J.: Red brick (1991), on North American New Music Festival Concert 184, April 11, 1992, 8:00 p.m.
NAF 619E. Parkinson, Stephen: Desires are already memories (1991), on North American New Music Festival Concert 184, April 11, 1992, 8:00 p.m.
NAF 619F. Tenney, James: Three new seeds (1991), on North American New Music Festival Concert 184, April 11, 1992, 8:00 p.m.
NAF 619G. Kucharzyk, Henry: All thumbs (1991), on North American New Music Festival Concert 184, April 11, 1992, 8:00 p.m.
NAF 619H. Stevenson, Robert W.: Present (1991), on North American New Music Festival Concert 184, April 11, 1992, 8:00 p.m.
NAF 619I. Smith, Linda Catlin: Passacaglia (1991), on North American New Music Festival Concert 184, April 11, 1992, 8:00 p.m.
NAF 619J. Butterfield, Christopher: Empress of Russia (1991), on North American New Music Festival Concert 184, April 11, 1992, 8:00 p.m.
NAF 619K. Longton, Michael: Arraymusic miniature (1991), on North American New Music Festival Concert 184, April 11, 1992, 8:00 p.m.
NAF 619L. Riley, Terry: Cactus rosary, a semi-secular song for Bruce Conner (1990), on North American New Music Festival Concert 184, April 11, 1992, 8:00 p.m.
NAF 629A. Raes, Godfried-Willem: Book of moves (1992-93), on North American New Music Festival Concert 189, October 29, 1993, 11:00 p.m.
NAF 640A. Harrison, Lou: Ibu Trish (1987-89), on North American New Music Festival Concert 192, October 30, 1993, 8:00 p.m.
NAF 640B. Timar, Andrew: Bintang at the Mangkunegaran. 2nd movement (1993), on North American New Music Festival Concert 192, October 30, 1993, 8:00 p.m.
NAF 640C. Siddall, Jon: Palace (1993), on North American New Music Festival Concert 192, October 30, 1993, 8:00 p.m.
NAF 640D. Cage, John: Haikai (1987), on North American New Music Festival Concert 192, October 30, 1993, 8:00 p.m.
NAF 640E. Harrison, Lou: Serenade (1978), on North American New Music Festival Concert 192, October 30, 1993, 8:00 p.m.
NAF 640F. Harrison, Lou: Main-Bersama-Soma (1978), on North American New Music Festival Concert 192, October 30, 1993, 8:00 p.m.
NAF 640G. Harrison, Lou: Threnody for Carlos Chavez (1979), on North American New Music Festival Concert 192, October 30, 1993, 8:00 p.m.
NAF 640H. Traditional: Sundanese gamelan music, on North American New Music Festival Concert 193, October 30, 1993, 11:00 p.m.
Related Resources
Related Resources in the Music Library
North American New Music Festival Archive, 1983-1995
Mus. Arc. 13
Finding aid for the administrative records and programs for the festival. It also includes a list of the photographs related to the festival.
North American New Music Festival Catalog, 1983-1993
The original inventory of the cassette recordings. It follows the original numbering of works and includes works that were performed but not recorded.
North American New Music Festival Archive Photographs
Digitized versions of the 173 photographs received with the Festival's papers.